let Questions = [
    {question: 'What is my name:',
        option: {
            a: 'uthman',
            b: 'Abdullah',
            c: 'seriki',
            d: 'school'
        }
        ,
        Answer: 'uthman',
        num: 1
    },
    {question: 'What is my school name:',
        option: {
            a: 'uthman',
            b: 'Mims',
            c: 'seriki',
            d: 'Eeman'
        }
        ,
        Answer: 'Mims',
        num: 2
    },
    {question: 'Find the coefficient of C in the expression <br> of (c-4) (c-5):',
        option: {
            a: '-9',
            b: '+9',
            c: '-1',
            d: '+1'
        }
        ,
        Answer: '-9',
        num: 3
    },
    {question: 'A ball is drawn at random from a box <br> containing 6 orange balls, 4 purple ball<br> and 5 blue balls. what is the probability<br> of picking a blue ball:',
        option: {
            a: '1/5',
            b: '2/5',
            c: '3/5',
            d: '1/3'
        }
        ,
        Answer: '1/3',
        num: 4
    },
    {question: 'Find the value of -3(xy -x<sup>2</sup>), if x= -1 <br>and y= -3:',
        option: {
            a: '10',
            b: '6',
            c: '-6',
            d: '-10'
        }
        ,
        Answer: '-6',
        num: 5
    },
    {question: 'Write the year 2015 in Roman Numeral',
        option: {
            a: 'MMLV',
            b: 'MXMV',
            c: 'MMXV',
            d: 'MMVX'
        }
        ,
        Answer: 'MMXV',
        num: 6
    },
    {question: 'Find the product of the L.C.M of 8 and<br> 12 and the H.C.F of 3 and 9:',
        option: {
            a: '60',
            b: '62',
            c: '64',
            d: '72'
        }
        ,
        Answer: '72',
        num: 7
    },
    {question: 'Find the next two terms in the sequence: <br> 2, 5, 9, 14, 20',
        option: {
            a: '27, 35',
            b: '26/30',
            c: '28/25',
            d: '24/26'
        }
        ,
        Answer: '27, 35',
        num: 8
    },
    {question: 'Evaluate(3<sup>3</sup>/<sub>4</sub> + 1<sup>1</sup>/<sub>2</sub>) &div; 7/12 ',
        option: {
            a: '-9',
            b: '+9',
            c: '-1',
            d: '+1'
        }
        ,
        Answer: '-9',
        num: 9
    },
    {question: 'A ball is drawn at random from a box <br> containing 6 orange balls, 4 purple ball<br> and 5 blue balls. what is the probability<br> of picking a blue ball:',
        option: {
            a: '1/5',
            b: '2/5',
            c: '3/5',
            d: '1/3'
        }
        ,
        Answer: '1/3',
        num: 10
    },
    {question: 'A ball is drawn at random from a box <br> containing 6 orange balls, 4 purple ball<br> and 5 blue balls. what is the probability<br> of picking a blue ball:',
        option: {
            a: '1/5',
            b: '2/5',
            c: '3/5',
            d: '1/3'
        }
        ,
        Answer: '1/3',
        num: 11
    },
    
];